

Contacts

Contacts: ±380974335970
Email: rudomanovdmitrjj@gmail.com
LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/
GIT: https://github.com/

Tech Skills

- HTML5
- CSS3
- scss
- GIT
- JavaScript
- WebPack
- React.js

Soft Skills

- Communication
- Teamwork
- Decision-making
- Leadership
- Creativity
- Stress management

Language Skills

Russian : NATIVEUkrainian : NATIVE

• English : Upper-intermediate

Front-End Developer

Dmitrij Rudomanov

I'm a Frontend developer with experience in building websites and APP's. Whether you're trying to win work, list your services or even create a whole online store – I can help! I'm experienced in HTML and CSS3, SCSS, JS and React. Regular communication is really important to me, so let's keep in touch!

Projects

1.	<u>'FILMOTEKA' web-site</u> [HTML5, CSS3, SCSS, JavaScript]
2.	'ICECREAM' web-site
3.	'WOODER' web-site [HTML5, CSS3, SCSS]
4.	'OFDR' Insurance web-site [HTML5, CSS3, SCSS, JavaScript
5.	'FUNIRO' web-store
6.	'LOGO' sport web-store
7.	'BENTLEY' web-site [HTML5, CSS3, SCSS, JavaScript]
8.	'BINARY' web-site [HTML5, CSS3, SCSS, JavaScript]
9.	'Prime-One' web-site
10.	'BIKE' web-site [HTML5, CSS3, SCSS, JavaScript]

Work Experience

Waiter Restaurant 'SHO PO CHEM'

June 2019 - September 2019 | Country Ukraine

- · Taking orders from visitors
- Customer service

Web-site editor Svet-LED Company

September 2019 - January 2019 | Country Ukraine

- Editing the list of products on the site
- · Products information update

Education

PSACEA

International Economics and business

September 2018 - June 2023 | Country Ukraine

Additional Education

GOIT

FULL STACK course online

August 2021 - June 2022 | Country Ukraine